(Gablehouser:)AA, I need your answer.
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
The answer is minus eight pi alpha.
(Sheldon:)Hang on a second.
That's not our answer.
(Sheldon:)- What are you doing?
- Answering question.
(Third Floor Janitor:)Winning Physics Bowl.
(Sheldon:)How do you know anything
about physics?
(Third Floor Janitor:)Here, I am janitor.
In former Soviet Union, I am physicist.
Leningrad Politechnika.
(Third Floor Janitor:)Go, Polar Bears.
(Sheldon:)That's a delightful little story.
(Sheldon:)Our arrangement was
you sit and not say anything.
(Sheldon:)- I answer the questions.
- You didn't answer question.
(Sheldon:)Hey, look. Now, maybe you have democracy
now in your beloved Russia...
(Sheldon:)...but on this Physics Bowl team,
I rule with an iron fist.
(Sheldon:)Ow!
(Gablehouser:)AA, I need your official answer.
(Sheldon:)- It's not what he said.
- Then what is it?
- I want a different question.
- You can't.